Thomas Pendleton

Anaheim, California, United States



thomaspendletondev@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/thomas-pendleton-330365133



https://thomaspendleton.netlify.app/

Summary

Seeking a position as Software Engineer in a professional setting that will enable me to learn new skills and have the ability to utilize the ones I have acquired through my education and work experience.

Knowledge in HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React, React Router, Redux and styled components.

Also a Master Automotive Technician, with over 15 years consistently learning new technologies and skills. Being self sufficient and efficient, diagnosing and repairing vehicles that are fixed right the first time.

Experience



Frontend Developer

Self-employed Jan 2022 - Present (10 months +)

Automotive Technician

BMW of North America, LLC Mar 2017 - Jan 2022 (4 years 11 months)

Automotive Technician

Volkswagen AG Feb 2008 - Mar 2017 (9 years 2 months)

• Automotive technician

Saab

Nov 2005 - Feb 2008 (2 years 4 months)

Education



Automotive diagnostic training center, anaheim

Basic clean air car course, Enhance area smog check license 2006 - 2006

Universal Technical Institute, Inc.

Automotive technology 2004 - 2005

Codecademy

Licenses & Certifications

- Ase recertified Master Technician A1-A8 ASE National Institute for Automotive Service Excellence
- ASE recertified L1 advanced engine performance ASE National Institute for Automotive Service Excellence
- Volkswagen Master Technician Volkswagen of America, Inc
- Enhanced area smog check technician Bureau Of Automotive Repair
- BMW level 3 technician BMW of North America, LLC
- Learn React Course Codecademy
- Building Interactive JavaScript Websites Course Codecademy
- Learn JavaScript Course Codecademy
- Learn Git & GitHub Course Codecademy
- Learn CSS Course Codecademy
- Learn Asynchronous JavaScript Course Codecademy
- Build a Website with HTML, CSS, and Github Pages Skill Path Codecademy

Skills

React.js • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • styled-components • Redux.js